I see people asking, what does Israel have to do with Texas?
And so I wanted to provide some more context because Israel is actively taking Texas taxpayer dollars and paying individual companies in Texas.
You, the Texans, are the ones getting cut out of that.
Meanwhile, your taxpayer dollars are being paid through bonds that provide the economic infrastructure to support the Israeli economy.
That Israeli economy is indirectly receiving free medical care, free education, housing subsidies, support, et cetera, via the support that your taxpayer dollars are giving to that country.
In the meantime, this nation, particularly your state as well, consistently tells you that you actually cannot get any of those things because that would be socialism.
And that's bad.
All of this is in addition to the fact that Israel is an apartheid state, that they are actively committing genocide, war crimes.
They are stealing homes and the lands and the lives of folks in the West Bank.
And they are consistently providing arms all over this globe to the destabilization of indigenous communities and black communities on the continent.
It is impossible to be for black rights and to consistently say you are in support of Israel because as we know, it is black communities that are always going to be forgotten first in every realm of the United States.
Whether we're talking about medical care, education, housing, voting rights, et cetera.
So if taxpayer dollars are being sent to Israel, circumventing the application of them to the actual constituency, who do you think is going to feel that the most?
For the record, your taxpayer dollars should not be going to another country, your taxpayer dollars should be going to supporting you, the taxpayer.
Now, this has been pretty hush hush for most of the American populace for quite some time.
However, I believe that because of the recent revelations of this, we are going to see the United States make a push to actually name Israel as an official extension of the United States, quashing any challenges of this.
Because in the same way that many states in the United States subsidize other states, your state will be subsidizing Israel.
However, if that money is going to Israel and then Israel sending money to the 1% who actually are not paying taxes, then doesn't it seem like you're getting cut out of it?
Yes, because you are.
Texas not only has an investment scheme set up with Israel, they have legislation that supports it.
Texas is even creating an outpost in Jerusalem for the purpose of investment.
Texas also does not allow for companies to get any level of contracts from Texas if they are involved in the boycott, divest, sanction movement against Israel.
Companies can also not receive any FEMA support if they are involved in the boycott, divest, sanction movement against Israel.
The town of San Marcos, Texas brought a resolution to the floor saying they wanted to divest from Israel because they were putting money into Israel bonds.
And Governor Abbott said, if you divest from Israel, I will divest from San Marcos and remove $4.4 million of Texas state grant money from supporting your town.
Your taxes are how that grant money comes into reality, y'all.
And that grant money is what organizers and artists and programs use to enrich your life and fill the gaps that the government is actually not doing when they should be.
So one of the ways this actually gets halted is if legislators stop capitulating, if they stop supporting it and if they stop feeding it.
Yes, it is going to require a large number of people.
But it starts with, at the very least, making demands that anyone entering the space is not going to do so on the backs of this.
Texas, not only do you deserve better, we all deserve better.
And the fact that the Congressional Black Caucus and Black leaders have supported this, knowing full well what's happening, is unacceptable.
And we simply cannot let it stand.
I know that hearing these truths can be inconvenient, especially when you already don't like me.
Nonetheless, I love you.
And so I want you to know so that we can actually do our best to protect ourselves and to challenge the folks who are supposed to represent us to do so in the best way possible.
To man, they care for Texans before Israel.
Listen to your people!
Because I hit hard!
Billionaires are the only minority we should be scared of!